(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-13T23:40:35.248724",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the performance starts.
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援 OK です
Due to staging, please be aware of flashing lights.
Vocal cheering is OK.
事前登録受付中！
Pre-registration now open!
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援 OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Vocal cheering is allowed!
Cheering loudly is ok.
事前登録受付中！
Pre-registration now open!
ローソンにお越しの皆さん！
Everyone visiting Lawson!
ローソンキャンペーン実施決定！
Lawson Campaign Confirmed!
今回はこの6人が登場！
These six members will appear this time!
詳細は3/9(月)公開予定！
Details to be revealed on Monday, March 9th!
EXPOのバンダイブースは大人気！
The Bandai booth at the EXPO is super popular!
注目の新商品も初公開！
First public reveal of featured new products!
会場限定、スペシャルフォトブース！
Venue-exclusive special photo booth!
ブースで限定カードがもらえる！
Get an exclusive card at the booth!
イベントブースでも公開！And MORE
Also revealed at the event booth! And MORE
来場せよ！
Come visit us!
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony
今年も hololive STAGE 1, 2, 3, 4
This year too, hololive STAGE 1, 2, 3, 4
Ridin' on Dreams JOYSOUND みるハコで配信決定！！
"Ridin' on Dreams" confirmed for distribution on JOYSOUND Miruhako!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there...
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say thank you over and over...
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now.
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's climb aboard!
ridin' on dreams
yeah!!
wow oh oh …
Wow oh oh...
hey!! (hey!!) hey!! (hey!!)
yeah!!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, starting from a small dream...
想像できないような
it turned into feelings...
想いになったんだ
that you couldn't even imagine.
わくわく止まらない!
The excitement just won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が船になる
our bonds become our ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety,
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
we can easily blow it all away.
果てない旅路を今
On this endless journey we row today,
漕いでる途中には困難もあるでしょう
there will surely be some hardships along the way.
それも力に変えて
We'll turn even those into strength,
一緒に進むんだよ!
and move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there...
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it can't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome even the rough waves...
“らしく”輝いていたい
and keep on shining in our own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, meeting you...
ねえ、宝物だから
is an absolute treasure to me.
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other...
地図など無い 未知の世界で
in this unknown world with no map...
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep going on and on!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh …
Wow oh oh...
hey!! (hey!!) hey!! (hey!!)
yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Even if a sudden wind...
行く先乱そうとも
tries to disturb our destination.
あの日誓ったんだ
We made a promise that day...
覚悟は揺るがない
our determination will never waver.
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
Having to stay strong, that push...
明日への橋になる
becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We need to cherish things even more...
“あたりまえ”は無いから
because nothing is ever guaranteed.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will start shortly. Please wait a moment.
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援 OK です
Please be aware of flashing lights during the show
Vocal cheering is allowed
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance
Cheering loudly is ok
PENLIGHT COLORS
事前登録受付中！
Pre-registrations are now open!
会場にいる同志諸君！ Stage3を震わせる！！！ 応援を！！！
[Tablet: To my fellow fans at the venue! Let's shake Stage 3!!! Give 'em your support!!!]
かなたん 6年間ありがとう
[Sign: Kanata, thank you for 6 years!]
輪堂788 ち RAV4
[Sign: Rindo 788 chi RAV4]
るーなたんすき♥
[Sign: I love Lu-na tan♥]
切って！
[Fan: Slice me up!]
AZKi's LOCATION!〜で鹿児島の温泉入りにきて！
[Sign: Come soak in a Kagoshima hot spring at AZKi's LOCATION!]
夢は叶えるためにある YAGOO
[Sign: Dreams exist to be fulfilled. - YAGOO]
永遠の天然ボケ イケメン師弟コンビ愛してる！！
[Sign: I love the eternal airhead cool mentor-student duo!!]
あずいろはいいぞ。
[Towel: AzIroha is great.]
牛丼はデザート
[T-shirt: Beef bowl is dessert]
からっとノオラ
[Phone Screen: Karatto Noora]
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' On Dreams
[Title: hololive 7th fes. Ridin' On Dreams]
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Harmony... the words we piled up
届けて
...reach out to you.
イェーイ！
Yeah!
あわただしく 駆け抜けては うつむかないと笑ってた
Running through in a rush, we laughed, promising not to look down.
未来予想 あの日の続きを見よう
Let's see the continuation of that day's future prediction.
手と手繋いで 風も着こなして
Hand in hand, styled even by the wind,
扉を叩いて 連れていくよ
we'll knock on the door and take you with us.
どんなことも きっと一緒なら 乗り越えていける
No matter what, as long as we're together, we can overcome it.
La la la la... 鳴り止まない 希望のベル ほら
La la la la... Look, the bell of hope won't stop ringing!
La la la la... 聞こえてる？ 歌
La la la la... Can you hear our song?
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Harmony... the words we piled up,
鮮やかな 日々の向こう
beyond the vivid days,
ずっと君と 響き合うストーリー
is a story that will always resonate with you.
ハートに結んだ夢が 空へ 駆けてゆく
The dream tied to our hearts races towards the sky,
きらめきを乗せて
carrying our sparkle.
あなたへ 届けて
Deliver to you,
メロディ どこまでも
this melody, infinitely.
何気ないことも 思い出す
Recalling even the casual, everyday things...
「大丈夫」じゃないよ、で深呼吸
"It's okay," no, take a deep breath
未体験楽しむ魔法の言葉
The magic words to enjoy untried experiences
一息ついて
Take a breath
振り返って
Look back
また君を知って その度に
Get to know you again, and every time
ちょっと勇気出して
Summon a little courage
明日へと飛び込んでいけ
And dive into tomorrow
La la la la...
塗りつぶす道標はまだ
The guidepost is still being painted over
La la la la...
覚えてる 歌
I remember the song
(覚えてる)
(I remember)
ハーモニー 手を伸ばしたら
Harmony, if I reach out my hand
足跡に虹が架かる
A rainbow will appear over our footprints
きっと晴れる
It will surely clear up
映し出すステージ
Reflecting on the stage
ハートに記した場所へ
To the place marked in my heart
運ぶ約束を
Carrying our promise
輝きにのせて
Riding on the radiance
世界へ
To the world
響け メロディ
Echo, melody!
いつまでも
Forever and ever
君と踏み出したあの一歩 あの瞬間が
That step I took with you, that moment
宝物だって胸を張る今
I hold my head high today, calling it my treasure
歩いて 話して はしゃいで 笑顔で行くんだ保存用
Walking, talking, having fun, let's go with a smile
色褪せないまま保存用
Without ever fading away
混ざり合う 僕らの声 ほら
Our voices blending together, look
聞こえてる 歌
I can hear the song
(聞こえてる)
(I can hear it)
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Harmony, our overlapping words
鮮やかな日々の向こう
Beyond those brilliant days
ずっと君と 彩るよストーリー
I'll always color the story with you
ハートに結んだ夢が
The dream tied to my heart
空へ駆けてゆく
Soars up into the sky
きらめきにのせて
Riding on the sparkle
あなたへ
To you
(あなたへ) 届け
(To you) Reach out
世界へ
To the world
(世界へ) 響け
(To the world) Echo
愛を
Love
(愛を) 込めて
(Love) filled with it
メロディ
Melody
どこまでも
To the ends of the earth
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
It's shining!
呼び合う声を合図に
With the voices calling each other as our signal
Parade, Parade, Parade!
探しにゆく
We go to search
スタートは何度だって
No matter how many times we start over
ただ 独り言を綴った
I just wrote down my monologues
ただ 始まりたくて走った
I just ran, wanting it to begin
遠く 暗がりに灯った
Lit far away in the darkness
それは 眩しすぎた名前
That was a name too dazzling
それは 優しすぎる思い出
Those are memories too kind
もっと
Even more...
近づけと手を伸ばした
I reached out my hand to get closer
思いがけず結び合った
Unexpectedly, we connected with each other
ほら 今
Look, now
迷子は
The lost children
“僕等”になった
Became "us"
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
It's shining!
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring both your frustrations and your love along
数え切れないコトバ
Countless words,
数えるような想いじゃないさ
are not feelings we can simply count.
ほら 今 僕らを 一つと呼ぼう
Look, now, let's call ourselves "one."
parade, parade, parade! 美しいんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! It's so beautiful.
許し合える刹那
The moments of forgiveness...
夜はきらめく
...shining in the night.
雨、晴れ、カレイド またとない空
Rain or shine, our kaleidoscope sky.
相応しい旅路とは 君と在ることさ
A journey made just for us is being with you,
君と在ることなんだ
standing right by your side.
“ただいま”を聞けば
When you're back and open that door,
“おかえり”って叫ぶよ
you'll hear us saying, "Welcome home!"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that only natural?
parade, parade, parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! We're gonna shine!
暗がりを満たすのは 君だ 僕だ!
What fills the darkness is you and me!
parade, parade, parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! We're gonna shine!
悔しさも愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring along both your frustration and love.
風、夢、羽 飛び立てるさ
Feel the wind, dreams, and wings; we can take flight!
ささやかな祈りは光 終わりなき兆し
These silent prayers are light, an endless sign.
君と 飛び込んでゆく 素敵なスタートさ
Ready to dive in with you, a beautiful start.
ここから これから our bright parade, parade!
Starting from here, right now, our bright parade!
フェスフェスフェス！ステージ3、行くよー！
Fes, fes, fes! Stage 3, here we go!
あの太陽よりもっと高く 手を伸ばして
Reach your hand out even higher than that sun!
長く伸ばした 季節色の影の上を
Over the long, season-colored shadows...
騒がしい足音で飾って
...decorating them with our noisy footsteps.
ワクワクする方へ向かおうか
Shall we head towards the direction of excitement?
決められた未来と違う風景ばっか行こうとしてる
I keep trying to go towards scenery different from my destined future.
間違ってないか がっかりしないか
Am I making a mistake? Will I end up disappointed?
散々迷って また今日に立っていた
After wandering lost for so long, I stood here again today.
誰も歩かない道の先で
At the end of a path that nobody walks...
霞んだ声がする
...a hazy voice echoes.
誰も気付けない予想外な
An unexpected tomorrow that no one noticed...
明日が今 ひらめいちゃったんだ
...has just flashed into my mind right now.
飛び出そう
Let's leap forward!
まだまだ音を重ねてゆく
We'll continue to layer more and more sounds.
みんなが変わってるって笑った毎日が
The days when everyone laughed and called me strange...
特別になるから
...are going to become special.
今この世界を愛しに行こう
Let's go love this world right now!
まっすぐ上ったまま消えない太陽に
Towards the sun that rose straight up and never fades...
手を伸ばして
...reach out your hand!
覚えてるんだ
I still remember:
初めは覚悟してた癖も
the habits I had prepared myself for at first,
恥ずかしくて語れない夢も
and the dreams too embarrassing to talk about.
一つ一つは特別に見えなくても
Even if each individual piece doesn't look special...
重なり合って ほら
...when they overlap, look—
今色めいた
they've taken on vibrant colors now.
まつりす！まつりに今を教えてくれて本当にありがとう！
Matsurisu! Thank you so much for showing me the present!
この曲は、まつりの覚悟の歌です！
This song is the song of Matsuri's determination!
これからも、まつりはまつりらしく突き進んでいくよ！
From here on out, Matsuri will keep forging ahead, true to herself!
まつりも君の居場所でいたいから！
Because Matsuri wants to be your place to belong!
大好きだぞー！
I love you so much!
間違ってないよ
You're not wrong!
がっかりしないで
Don't be disappointed.
さんざんな道が一番楽しんだ
A disastrous road is the most fun of all!
なんだろう ちょっとだけ頭がズレてゆく
I wonder why... my head is spinning just a little.
みんなと違ってるって凹んだ毎日が
The days I felt down for being different from everyone...
きっと最高になるから
...are sure to become the absolute best!
今から世界をハグしに行こう
Let's go hug the world starting now!
すっかりのぼったまま消えない太陽を
Chasing after the sun that has risen completely...
追いかけて
...and will never fade!
セッションしよう
Let's have a session!
まわるまわる音を 追いかけてゆく
We'll chase after the spinning, revolving sound!
みんなと変わってるって笑った毎日が
The days we laughed about being different from everyone...
突然特別になるから
...will suddenly become special!
今すぐ世界に恋しに行こう
Let's go fall in love with the world right now!
あの上空の眩しさに 毎回くらいに
With the brightness of that high sky, nearly every time...
手を伸ばして
...reach out your hand!
Everybody put your hands up!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Wake up, another bloody Monday
Say things I never wanted to say
Keep an arm's length, can't please
Live and play by day
Wake up, another bloody Monday
And spin the wheel until it's Sunday
Oh, it's so frustrating
You know I can't do it no more
I'll say...
No, go down to the core
Hear you knock and beat down my door
Get out, scream and shout
But I'll never change now
I'm just too much, but not enough to please your eyes
No, I'm never, never, never...
Your idea of ideals that you're screaming in my head
I'm just so broken inside
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
Won't stop me
We'll never figure it out
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
You and me, the norm, are just so-so
Moving in a hurry, in over my head
I'm a little bit too slow, I'm just gonna let it go
But the end is sudden, end of your perfection, correction
Tearing me down, am I what you like?
Now don't tell me what to do
What to say, what to think about everything
But tell you everything
I'll say...
Can't fit the fitting, so what's the issue?
I'll screw up again
Get out, scream and shout
But I'll never change now
I'm just too much, but not enough to please your eyes
No, I'm never, never, never...
Your idea of ideals that you're screaming in my head
I'm just so broken inside
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
Unstoppable, I'm static
Fly like it's my way, get it
Beautiful, fragile
Bitter, sweet, cold ice... so what?
To make your heart cry to you
Too bad I'm never gonna, I'm never gonna fail
Oh, no...
Get out, scream and shout
But I'll never change now
I'm just too much, but not enough to please your eyes
No, I'm never, never, never...
Your idea of ideals that you're screaming in my head
I'm just so broken inside
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
Won't stop me
We'll never figure it out
No, never, never let go, think of it else!
こんまっする！白銀ノエルです！
Kon-muscle! I'm Shirogane Noel!
みんな！盛り上がっていくぞー！
Everyone! Let's get pumped up!
終わらない 終わらない 仕事山積み 終わらない
Never ending, never ending! The pile of work never ends!
止まらない 止まらない それでも時間は止まらない
Non-stopping, non-stopping! Even so, time doesn't stop!
ヘトヘト たまりにたまったヘトヘト
Exhausted! All of my built-up exhaustion!
木製バット 打ち返すバット コンボを制する金属バット
Wooden bat! Swings and hits back! A metal bat dominating the combos!
今日も手一杯 今日も手一杯
My hands are full today too, my hands are full today too!
No more 悪あがき ギミーギミージュースィー
No more useless struggling, gimme gimme juicy!
細くなりたい 細くなりたい
I want to be slim! I want to be slim!
ため息ブレスで MPすっからかん
With a sighing breath, my MP is completely empty!
自分自身に厳しすぎちゃう
I'm way too strict on myself!
すぐヘラヘラヘラヘラ言う統制 さっぱり足りない柔軟性
Constantly grinning under control, completely lacking in flexibility!
自分自身としっかり向き合う
Face myself directly and honestly!
一番必要なものは
The thing I need the absolute most is...
トレビアン ご褒美ちょうだい
Très bien! Give me a reward!
てんてこ舞うようなリズムにバイバイしちゃえ
Say bye-bye to this hectic rhythm!
ドレミファノートに5ライン
Five lines on a Do-Re-Mi-Fa notebook!
ぎゅうぎゅうと詰めちゃダメ もう一回！
Don't cram it in so tightly! One more time!
トレビアン ご褒美ちょうだい
Très bien! Give me a reward!
てんてこ舞うようなリズムにバイバイしちゃえ
Say bye-bye to this hectic rhythm!
ドレミファノートに5ライン
Five lines on a Do-Re-Mi-Fa notebook!
ぎゅうぎゅうと詰めちゃダメ どんどんフリーダム
Don't cram it in so tightly! Freedom, on and on!
ぎゅうぎゅうと詰めちゃダメ ご褒美どんどん好きになる
Don't cram it in so tightly! I'll love my rewards more and more!
ぎゅうどん！ぎゅうどん！どん！
Gyudon! Gyudon! Don!
ぎゅうどん！ぎゅうどん！どん！どん！
Gyudon! Gyudon! Don! Don!
ぎゅうどん！ぎゅっとして どーん！
Gyudon! Give me a tight hug and kaboom!
さあさ牛丼だ 牛丼だ
Come on, it's gyudon, it's gyudon!
一緒に食べよう
Let's eat together!
黄身と仲良く かーにばる
A carnival to get along with the egg yolk!
トロトロちゅわわ
Melty-melty, chu-wa-wa!
ほろりお肉 お肉
Tender meat, tender meat!
つまんじゃダメ
Don't pinch it!
全部食べたら ほめちゃう
If you eat it all, I'll praise you!
なでなで よしよし ちゅっちゅっ
Pat-pat, there-there, kiss-kiss!
あびゃ！あびゃあびゃ！
Abya! Abya-abya!
あびゃあびゃあびゃあびゃあびゃあびゃ
Abya-abya-abya-abya-abya-abya!
あびゃあびゃあびゃ あびゃ！ 洗脳開始！
Abya-abya-abya abya! Brainwashing start!
すっきー！すきすき大ちゅっきー！
Love! Love-love, I love you so much!
らっびゅー！らぶらぶ洗脳中ー
Love you! Love-love brainwashing in progress!
むっちー！むちむち責めちゃダメー
Muchie! Don't blame my chubby cheeks!
よく出来ました ほっぺにちゅっ
You did a great job! A kiss on the cheek!
だくだく ねぎだく えいっ
Lots of, lots of green onions, yah!
ところが全然足りません
But it's not nearly enough at all!
だくだく つゆだく わぁ
Lots of, lots of broth, wow!
それでも全然足りません
Even so, it's not nearly enough at all!
だくだく にくだく あぁん
Lots of, lots of meat, ah!
まだまだ全然足りないの！
It's still not nearly enough at all!
だくだく どくどく きゅんっ
Thump-thump, heavy thumping, heart squeeze!
ドキがムねムね止まらなーい！
My heart is thumping and won't stop!
牛丼を食べるときは
When eating gyudon,
お口でふーふーってして...
make sure to blow on it first...
あっ、いきなりがっついちゃって、かわいい
Ah, you started scarfing it down already, cute!
優しく...丁寧に、だぞ？
Be gentle and careful, okay?
あははっ、いい子いい子
Ahaha, good child, good child.
...おなか、いっぱいになっちゃったね
...Your tummy is all full now.
...一緒に、寝ちゃう？
...Shall we sleep together?
おやすみなさいー
Good night~
もしも キミが シュンとしちゃっても
Even if you feel down sometimes,
ぎゅーって ぎゅーって ぎゅーって！
Tightly, tightly, tightly!
抱きしめたげる
I will hug you!
いくよ！幕張ーー！
Here we go, Makuhari!
さあさ牛丼だ 牛丼だ
Come on, it's gyudon, it's gyudon!
一緒に食べよう
Let's eat together!
キミと何度でも かーにばる
A carnival with you over and over again!
トロトロちゅわわ
Melty-melty, chu-wa-wa!
ほろりお肉 お肉
Tender meat, tender meat!
つまんじゃダメ
Don't pinch it!
全部食べたら ほめちゃう
If you eat it all, I'll praise you!
なでなで よしよし ちゅっちゅっ
Pat-pat, there-there, kiss-kiss!
あびゃ！
Abya!
せーの、ぎゅーどん！
Ready, set, gyudon!
大好き！
I love you!
ぎゅっとしてどーん！
Give me a tight hug and kaboom!
まだまだどーん！
More and more, kaboom!
みんなと唱えるの ぎゅーどん！
Chanting together with everyone, gyudon!
ぎゅーーーっ！
Tight squeeze!
ありがとうーー！
Thank you so much!
響咲リオナ
Isaki Riona
虎金妃笑虎
Koganei Niko
水宮枢
Mizumiya Su
輪堂千速
Rindo Chihaya
綺々羅々ヴィヴィ
Kikirara Vivi
You'll see !
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it ? Break it ?
Make it? Break it?
Lock on
目と目が合えば I know
When our eyes meet, I know
キミこそが相棒
you are the one, my partner.
メロつかせる才能
A talent to make them swoon...
Make it ? Break it ? Make it ? Break it ?
Make it? Break it? Make it? Break it?
パッと見天使でも
Even if I look like an angel at first glance,
中には潜むデーモン
there's a demon lurking inside.
So ギャップと愛嬌あれば最強
So with gap moe and charm, I'm the strongest.
Haterはシカト「へー、あっそ！」
Ignoring the haters, like, "Oh, really?"
一蓮托生オーガナイズ
An organization bound by fate,
退屈に用は無い
we have no use for boredom.
一線画すよボーダーライン
We'll draw a clear borderline.
届かない？しょーがない
Can't reach us? Too bad!
ウチらが集えばバリ baddest
When we gather, we're the baddest.
見惚れちゃうでしょ？
You're captivated, aren't you?
Look at me, look at me, look at me now...
置いてかない絶対
I'll never leave you behind,
ついて来て 5MC's
so follow the 5 MCs.
本気のフライデーナイト
A Friday night of playing for keeps,
Make it ? Break it ?
make it, break it!
Make a revolution
アタシを貫け傾け
Stay true to yourself, stand out!
夢に強引 going, going on !
Pushing aggressively towards our dreams, going, going on!
Break through and never stop
真ん中ぶち抜け行け
break right through the center!
Can't get enough
You'll see !
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it ? Break it ?
Make it? Break it?
Bang ! bang ! bang !
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You'll see !
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it ? Break it ?
Make it? Break it?
ほら、どっちにするの？
Hey, which one will you choose?
有象無象沸かす flow glow
Stirring up the masses, Flow Glow,
Ay 口先より行動
actions speak louder than words.
If you wanna be マイメン
If you wanna be my men,
よそ見とかナシで
don't look anywhere else.
Warning ! 没頭ほら没頭ほら
Warning! Immerse yourself, look, immerse yourself,
味わっちゃって
savoring the moment.
Burning ! もっと hotter もっと hotter
Burning! Getting hotter, hotter,
ハイになっちゃって
getting so high.
置いてかない絶対
I'll never leave you behind,
ついて来て 5MC's
so follow the 5 MCs.
本気のフライデーナイト
A Friday night of playing for keeps,
Make it ? Break it ?
make it, break it!
Brand new generation
感じるままアガれアガれ
Rise up, rise up, just as you feel!
華麗に降臨 only, only one
A magnificent descent, the only, only one!
退屈な Neverland
The boring Neverland,
速攻で抜け出せ I say
break out of there immediately, I say!
Ready or not ?
Ready or not?
You'll see !
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it ? Break it ?
Make it? Break it?
Bang ! bang ! bang !
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You'll see !
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it ? Break it ?
Make it? Break it?
朝まで make some noise
Make some noise until morning!
盛り上がり
Let's get hyped,
それじゃ
and then...
Make a revolution
アタシを貫け傾け
Stay true to yourself, stand out,
夢に強引 going, going on !
pushing aggressively towards our dreams, going, going on!
Break through and never stop
真ん中ぶち抜け行け
break right through the center!
Can't get enough
You'll see !
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it ? Break it ?
Make it? Break it?
Bang ! bang ! bang !
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You'll see !
You'll see!
Make it or break it
Make it ? Break it ?
Make it? Break it?
ほら、どっちにするの？
Hey, which one will you choose?
わあー！
Wow!
What's up, せーの！
What's up! Ready, go!
キープ・ローリング！
Keep Rolling!
Flow Glow です！
We are Flow Glow!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
皆さん、私たちのステージ見てくれてありがとうございます！
Everyone, thank you so much for watching our stage performance!
まずは私たちの自己紹介からさせてください！
First, please let us introduce ourselves!
まずは私から！
Starting with me first!
皆さん、私が「おかえりおな、おかえりおな、おかえりおな〜」って言ったら、みんなで「ただいまレゴ！」って言ってほしいです！
Everyone, when I say "Okaeriona, Okaeriona, Okaeriona~", I want you all to say "Tadaima Rego!"
そして挨拶の最後の「ブラブラ〜」も「せーの」って言うので、よかったら一緒に言ってください！いいですか？
And at the end of the greeting, when I say "Ready, go!" for "Bura bura~", please say it with me! Are you ready?
はーい！
Yes!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いきます！
Here I go!
おかえりおな、おかえりおな、おかえりおな〜！
Okaeriona, Okaeriona, Okaeriona~!
ただいまレゴ！
Tadaima Rego!
ありがとう！おかえり！
Thank you! Welcome back!
私の元においで！
Come to me!
リオナ・イン・ザ・ハウス！
Riona in the house!
Flow Glow のリーダー、響咲リオナです！
I'm Isaki Riona, the leader of Flow Glow!
せーの！
Ready, go!
ブラ！ブラ！
Bura! Bura!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
めっちゃ嬉しい！
I'm so incredibly happy!
もう本当に今ここでみんなと会えたこと、すごく幸せです！
I'm truly so happy that I got to meet everyone here right now!
そして Flow Glow のみんなとここでステージを、この日を迎えられたこと、とても幸せに思います！
And I feel so happy to welcome this stage, this day, with everyone in Flow Glow!
今日は一日楽しんでいくぞー！
Let's have an amazing time today!
オー！
Yeah!
続いて...
Next up...
あ、はい！
Oh, yes!
ニコ、いくぞ！
Niko, here we go!
ニコとが〜
Niko to ga~
きたー！
Kita~!
ホロライブデバイス、Flow Glow のお笑い担当、虎金妃笑虎です！
I'm Koganei Niko, the comedy representative of hololive DEV_IS, Flow Glow!
ニコ足りないよ！
I don't have enough Niko!
ニコ！
Niko!
なー、嬉しい。え、ニコたんもこれ、コールアンドレスポンスってやつやってもいい？
I'm so happy. Hey, can Nicotan do this call-and-response thing too?
もちろん、もちろん！
Of course, of course!
じゃあ「ニコたんはー」って言ったら、トラだと思う人は「トラ」って言って、ヒトだと思う人は「ヒト」って言ってください。
So when I say, "Nicotan is...", those who think I'm a tiger, say "Tiger!", and those who think I'm human, say "Human!"
えー？どっちだろう？どっちもいいな。
Huh? Which one? Both are good.
オッケー、オッケー。わかった？いくよ！ニコたんはー？
Okay, okay. Got it? Here we go! Nicotan is...?
ヒト！
Human!
お前らとは今日が最後のステージ...
Today is my last stage with you guys...
やだー！違う、違う！
No way! That's not it!
やだ、やだ！そして？
No way! And next?
はい！えーっと、すー、あ、すーが「しゅぴしゅわ、すーの充電」って言ったら、「足りてるー！」って言ってください！
Yes! Um, when Su- when Su says, "Shupishuwa, Su's charging!", please say, "You have enough!"
はーい！
Okay!
しゅぴしゅわ、すーの充電？
Shupishuwa, Su's charging?
足りてるー！
You have enough!
ありがとう！フロウグロウの偉いセンター、タコと水のスーです！
Thank you! The great center of FloGlow, octopus and water's Su!
嬉しい！偉いね！
I'm so happy! Great, right?
すーは今日もでっかいです！次、ビビ！
Su is big today too! Next, Bibi!
ん？おら！
Huh? Hey!
おら！おらおらおらおら！ごめん！
Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey! Sorry!
轟、轟！ごめん、ごめん、そっち？あれ？
Todoroki, Todoroki! Sorry, sorry, that way? Huh?
ありがとうございます！本当にごめん。はい。では、「エンジン全開」って言ったら、「レッツゴー」って言ってください！
Thank you very much! Truly sorry. Yes. So, when I say "Engine Zenkai!", please say "Let's Go!"
お願いします。いきますよ？エンジン全開！
Please. Here we go! Engine Zenkai!
レッツゴー！
Let's Go!
やったー！ありがとうございます！DJ系運転手こと轟はじめです！やったー！
Yay! Thank you very much! The DJ-style driver, Todoroki Hajime! Yay!
そして最後に？
And finally?
はい！皆さん、ビビは、もうわかるよな、みんな！ビビが「せーの」って言ったら、「うー」で...
Yes! Everyone, you all know what to do for Bibi, right? When Bibi says "Ready, set...", with a "Woo...", you...
あ、まだ早い！まだ早い！
Ah, too early! Too early!
まだ早い、まだ早い。
Too early, too early.
幕張でお漏らしです。やめて！
Wetting herself at Makuhari. Stop it!
コラコラ！お漏らしやめて！今のは予行練習ね、みんな。準備バッチリね？
Hey, hey! Stop the wetting herself talk! That was just a rehearsal, everyone. Are you completely ready?
みんな、声出す準備できてるかー？
Is everyone ready to let their voices out?
せーの！うー、
Ready, set... Woo,
ビビ！
Bibi!
わー！みんなありがとう！いつもキラキラな、キ・キ・ラ・ラ、ビビです！うわー！
Wow! Thank you everyone! Always sparkling, Ki-Ki-Ra-Ra, Bibi! Wow!
ビビ！ビビ！
Bibi! Bibi!
はい！ということでね、ホロライブフェスステージ3が始まりました！2日目の夜になります！
Yes! And so, Hololive Fes Stage 3 has begun! It is now the night of Day 2!
会いたかったよ、みんなー！温まってるか？温まってる？
We wanted to see you, everyone! Are you warmed up? Warmed up?
そしてですね、今回はなんと新しい試みが。
And also, this time there is actually a new attempt...
あ、でもハッシュタグをその前に。そうですね。
Ah, but the hashtag before that. That's true.
ハッシュタグからいきますか、まずは。ハッシュタグは？
Let's start with the hashtag first. The hashtag is...?
ホロライブフェスエキスポ26デイ2、です！
"hololivefesEXPO26_DAY2"!
デイ2、デイ2、デイ2ですよ！
Day 2, Day 2, it's Day 2!
みんなたくさんポストしてね！
Everyone, post a lot, okay!
はい、じゃあ続いて、さっきの今日の...
Yes, so next, about earlier today's...
今回、そう、トロッコがね！
This time, yes, the trolley!
みんなの客席に来たんじゃないですか？
Didn't we go right into your seats?
どうだった？近くで見れましたか？フログロウを。
How was it? Did you get to see FloGlow up close?
ちょっと太もも近すぎた気がする。
I feel like our thighs were a bit too close.
皆さんから下から見られる太ももちょっと恥ずかしかったわ。
Being looked at from below by everyone, the thighs were a bit embarrassing.
太もも最高でした？ビビのお尻もやばいから！
Were the thighs the best? Bibi's butt was crazy too!
やばいやばいやばい！何やってんの！やりたい放題！
Oh my god, what are you doing! Doing whatever we want!
これ俺らのステージだから！やりたい放題！
This is our stage! Doing whatever we want!
あと、あと何だっけ？ずるいずるい！そんなんずるい！
And, what was next? Unfair, unfair! That's so unfair!
やめましょうね、元に戻りましょう。
Let's stop. Let's go back to normal.
言うことあるんじゃないの？ということで、YouTubeやTikTokでご覧の方は、なんと！
Don't you have something to say? So, for those watching on YouTube or TikTok, actually...!
ここまでになってしまいます！
This is where it ends for you!
やだー！
No way!
こんな感じでね、ている方はですね、ぜひあの概要欄から配信チケット買えますので、
For those watching there, you can buy streaming tickets from the description box,
こういう風になっちゃってる方はぜひよろしくお願いします。
so if you're in this situation, please do so.
このあと5人で合体するところも見られないわけでしょう？
You won't even be able to see the 5 of us combine after this, right?
やらない、やらない、やらないからね！
We're not doing it, we're not doing it!
ということでね、ここまでということで。最後に私たちも合体するということで...
So, this is the end for the free part. Finally, we will also combine...
会場のみんなと合体しよう！
Let's combine with everyone in the venue!
みんなと合体していきたいと思います！
We'd like to combine with all of you!
ということで、なんと私たちからのお願いがありまして。
So, we actually have a favor to ask of you.
私たちここ5分割くらいかな？目の前のメンバーに、ペンライトのカラーを変えてもらうことってできたりしますか？
Can you guys split into about 5 sections and change your penlight colors to match the member standing right in front of you?
みどり！ お願いします！
Green! Please!
ライト、みどり！ ピンク、ピンク！
Green lights! Pink, pink!
ペンライト、ピンクにして！
Turn your penlights pink!
わあ、ありがとう！ ありがとうございます！
Wow, thank you! Thank you so much!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
きれいだね！
It's so beautiful!
よし！
Alright!
やっぱり私たちもフェスに出られたということで
Since we're performing at the festival too,
先輩たちがいつもやってるウェーブやりたいよね！
we want to do that wave the seniors always do, right?
やりたい、やりたい！
We do, we do!
じゃあ、私から「うにょーん」って行くから
Then, I'll start with a "Unyon," so...
え？ うにょーん？
Eh? "Unyon"?
下がればいい？ 上がればいい？
Should we go down? Or up?
こうじゃない？ あ、間違えた、間違えた。
Isn't it like this? Ah, my mistake, my mistake.
走るんで...
We'll run, so...
そうやって、そうやって！
Like that, like that!
そう、私たちがいるところを「いー！」ってやってもらえると
Yes, if you go "Eee!" where we are...
まあ、みんな慣れてるよね！
Well, you're all used to this, right!
オッケー！
Okay!
行くよ、こっちから！ ゆっくりね。
Here we go, starting from this side! Slowly, okay?
はい、じゃあ始めよう。
Alright, let's start.
あっちに向かって走ろうよ。
Let's run towards that side.
オッケー、わかった。 こっちから。
Okay, got it. Starting from here.
しおなの色からですよ！
Starting with Shiona's color!
しおなの色からですね、じゃあ、行きますよ！
Starting with Shiona's color, okay, here we go!
はい、せーの！
Alright, ready, set, go!
ピピピピピピ...
Pi-pi-pi-pi-pi...
あ、来た、来た！
Ah, it's coming, it's coming!
おおー！
Ohhh!
おお、すごい、すごい！
Oh, amazing, amazing!
ピピピピピピ... 戻って、戻って！
Pi-pi-pi-pi-pi... And back, and back!
いえーい！
Yay!
すごい！ ありがとう！
Amazing! Thank you!
はーい、じゃあ戻ります。
Alright, let's go back to our spots.
はい、ということで、幸せな時間をありがとうございました！
Yes, and with that, thank you for this wonderful, happy time!
じゃあ、最後の決めゼリフ、行きますか！
Then, shall we do our final catchphrase?
行きますか！ 行きましょう！
Let's do it! Let's go!
じゃあみんな、魂込めて、今日の思いをすべて込めて言いましょう！
Alright, everyone, let's put our souls into it, pouring all of today's feelings!
行きますよ、せーの！
Here we go, ready, set...
ライディオン...
Ridin' on...
ドリームズ！
Dreams!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！